You
Please tell me it worked even if just for a second
If it did then someone should be able to behead him
I
Of course
Not a day goes by that I don't
I
I always think about the day I left my homeland with you three
It feels like only yesterday it happened
Hey this one's tasty too
Come on join me
Right
It's delicious
Slow down
Would it kill you to show restraint?
Settle down
But Lord Tengen told us to dig in
Here you go Makyo, open wide
It is good
Isn't it?
In the end I'm going straight to hell
Whoops
Shouldn't have said that out loud
I guess I just earned another tongue lashing from you three, huh?
Mark my words
I'm gonna live the flashiest life possible for my fallen siblings
With you three
Right
How lovely
Oh
You didn't have to do that
No?
Lord Tengen, look at this
I've got a few in my hair too
Why do I feel like you put those on yourself?
What did you think I would do that?
Lord Tengen
If you don't mind
Could you give me that petal?
I don't mind at all
But there's tons of them everywhere
The only one I want is that one
Thank you Lord Tengen
Lord Tengen I want one too!
Huh?
Just pick up one of the petals yourself
You're so cruel
Lord Tengen
He regenerated his legs?
Damn it!
He's already neutralized the poison!
Man...
That poison sure packed a punch
But now it's my turn
Blood demon heart
Rotating circular slashes
Flying blood size!
He can attack without swinging his arms
Such range!
Sound breathing
Fourth form
Constant resounding slashes!
He's gone?
No
I'll draw the belt's attention
Don't mind me
I'll take care of her
You find that demon
You've got some nerve jumping into this fight
But now you have to suffer the consequences of that choice
Minatsuru!
Dammit!
These belts!
Are blocking me!
Minatsuru!
Wow!
It's beautiful here!
Don't you think Lord Tengen?
Dragonflies!
I wish I could slur like one of them
Hey!
Now that's a flashy dream if I ever heard one
There you go again spouting nonsense like a lunatic
What?
Why do you have to be so mean all the time?
I hate you Makyo!
What was that?
I dare you to say that again!
Lord Tengen
Once we've defeated an upper rank demon
What do you think about us all stepping back from the front lines?
And just living as civilians?
While none of us chose to become shinobi
We can't just walk away after all the lives we took
We still need to set things right somewhere along the line
Otherwise we can never hold our heads up again or dream of ever living a normal life
When that day comes one of us might not make it
But no hard feelings, right?
Leave her alone!
Move!
Move! Move! Move! Move! Move!
Another person is about to be killed before my eyes!
Close the distance! Quick! Jump up on the roof!
You can't always be the one being protected!
You have to be useful here!
Because I'm weak, he doesn't acknowledge me as a threat!
So if I make an unpredictable move, I can save her!
I have no choice!
I have to use Hinokami Kagura!
Maybe I can reach him with that!
It's no good!
I'm out of stamina!
I can't pull it off!
What do I do?
Think!
Focus!
What else can I do right now that's going to be able to save her?
I have to act before it's too late!
I didn't think that kid was capable of such a light and quick move.
Judging from his fatigue, there's no way he can move like that again right now.
I did it! I did it!
Keep blending the breathing techniques!
Use water breathing and Hinokami Kagura in combination!
That'll give me more attack power than I'd have with just water breathing!
And I'll also be able to move longer than with just Hinokami Kagura!
I bet the swordsmen who have fought the demons till now have been doing that all along!
Pairing the breathing techniques with the sword skills that suit them best!
And modifying them into a form that draws out their full power!
I'm sure those same swordsmen were able to create different techniques like that!
Modify it into any form!
Be flexible!
That's the kind of fighting style that Mr. Urokodaki taught me to use!
Even if I can never fully master water breathing like Mr. Tomioka!
No matter what, I won't let what Mr. Urokodaki taught me go to waste!
Enough fooling around! You're going down!
Tanjiro Kamado!
You have my utmost gratitude!
Watch it! There's too many of these things to keep up with!
They might be slithery, but these things are hard as a rock!
There's no end in sight to them either!
Damn it, damn it! They're gonna decapitate him without me!
Inosuke! Incoming attack!
The only way to bring this one down is for us to strike at the same time!
We're able to hold our own by dodging her belt attacks, but we can't expect to win just by avoiding her!
We have to act! If we can close the distance, we can go for her head!
Inosuke! Calm down! We don't have to strike simultaneously! We just need to make sure the two demon heads aren't connected!
Even after they've beheaded their demon, we have to fight with all we've got!
Wait, you're... you're like...
You're like a completely different person now, aren't you?
What gives?
Stay alert! And use this chance to go for his head!
I can do it!
Damn!
It will punch!
You really think you're capable of cutting off my head? Hate to break it to you, but that's not gonna happen!
My blade is stuck!
Of course, a freak like you can swing his head all the way around like that!
Not again!
Kamado! Hang on tight!
Mr. Ozui!
Lord Tengan!
Look out!
Inosuke! Send him to!
They're forcing us to change our strategy!
Muzzle!
I can't close in on the worm lady no matter what!
So us three will take her on while the old man deals with the pregnantus guy alone!
Well, at the very least, she's the weaker of the two!
We need to behead her first!
Tanjiro, can you still move?
Uh-huh!
I can move!
However, Mr. Ozui has been poisoned and he's in bad shape because of it!
So we have to hurry!
Or else he won't make it!
I barely blocked it!
That was close!
He's attacking us even as he fights Mr. Ozui!
Miss Inatsuru!
You shouldn't worry about me at all!
I'll hide for now!
You just focus on winning!
Look out!
Behind you!
Are you alright?
Yes, thanks to you!
I can see that your movements are getting more and more sluggish!
I wonder which of you will be the first to fall apart!
Damn it!
Monichi and I are still practically unscathed!
We've got to start getting serious!
The other two are banged up from giving their all!
What was the point of all that Peril training?
What was the point?
What was the point of all that Peril training is?
I don't care!
This demon's neck is too soft to cut normally!
It's going to take a lot of speed, otherwise we'll have to slash her from multiple directions!
Got that!
Now that it's heading toward Tandreau as well, it seems like the attack has ever so slightly slowed down!
Maybe I'm saying things here!
I'm going to assume it has!
Alright!
If you want multiple directions, leave it to yours truly!
Lordy Nosuke the dual wielder!
As long as you two have my back, together we can beat her!
Understood!
Sandy 2, protecty Nosuke!
Got it!
You can bring all the ugly freaks you want to the fight, but it's not going to change a thing!
Now I know scare!
Let's go!
Stay close and don't let me down, Underling!
Peace, brother!
Ain't fun!
Explosive!
Rush!
Water breathing!
Third form!
Thunder breathing!
First form!
Blowing!
Thunderclap and Flash!
Dance!
Fall!
What?
He's charging straight towards me without any type of defense!
I'm getting it done this time!
You can't cut it off!
There's no way you can!
Not with these beat up blades of yours!
Sixth frame!
No!
Exft frame!
Palisade-Bite!
Right
He knows get you did it using your swords like saw blades was genius
I got her head. I got her head. I'm gonna take it far away so she can't stick it back on
You two go help the old man. I'm gonna run around with this head until you guys beat the other one
Will do be careful you nose gay. Got it. Mr. Uzo-weep
We've got to help him before it's too late
Yeah
Is that all you guys men you suck now
You might not die when your head is good off, but you're so damn weak you might as well be dead
Inosuke
He knows get he knows get this is bad the poison was he stabbed in the heart
It's too dark to see damn it
What's he doing here? He was fighting mr. Uzo-wee
Mr. Uzo-wee
Tanjiro look out
Damn it
Sany2 forget about me
This happened because I wasn't paying attention
I'm sorry he knows get if only I'd noticed him sooner than maybe
No, if I hadn't left mr. Uzo-wee side in the first place. This never would have happened
It's my fault. I'm sorry everyone
Please forgive me
I'm sorry
Naizuko
fall
Thank you.
Don't give up.
Don't give up!
Next! Episode 10!
Never give up!